He's always very neutral with people.
He compromises to get along with
me and my difficult personality.
He doesn't have any preconceptions about me.
He appreciates all the effort and
hard work I try not to let people see.
He understands what I'm like.
So I want to get to know him better.
I wish I could understand him, too.
Asamura Yuta...
I'm attracted to him.
He's the kind of guy who
pays attention to detail.
THE BEEHIVE
TAMURA KANAE
Just out on August 22!
It took him no time to find a book
I'd spent ten minutes searching for.
But then, when he told me she
would've found it even quicker...
I realized how small-minded
I must be, and it frustrates me.
The next day... Isn't that when
the AC in the living room broke?
That evening, Asamura-kun confronted me.
He asked if Maaya had
invited us to go to the pool.
Oh.
I don't even want to
remember how I reacted.
Then you don't need to force yourself to go.
I mean, I can't waste my time playing.
Aren't you going? To the pool?
I just can't.
No, I'm not.
I think I was really at my limit.
I lashed out at him with
a dismissive response
because I didn't want to
hear any more about it.
I'm going on ahead
What I said was so harsh, I can hardly
believe it came from my own mouth.
I don't
want to.
Yeah, thanks.
I sounded like a child.
That was such a horrible day.
The worst part was that I knew
I was having these awful thoughts,
but I didn't want to be
forced to deal with them.
She has such long, beautiful hair.
Even I think it's lovely.
It suits Asamura-kun's modest style.
I wonder if he likes girls
with long, pretty hair.
At least my hair is long, too.
What in the world am I thinking? Seriously...
After finishing dinner,
he brought it up again.
He said he wanted me
to go have fun at the pool.
Why is he worried about something like that?
I need to spend my time studying.
I can't afford to go out and play.
Ah, I've seen that look before.
When I was in middle school,
there was one time when Mom
wanted to take me to the beach.
Considering our financial situation,
I didn't think we could afford it.
It's okay. I've got tests coming up.
I didn't want to force Mom
to take a day off work.
Okay, maybe next time.
That's when she made that face.
A kind of disappointed look.
Sunday, August 6th.
We're at the beach today.
Oh, Yuta! Don't run, okay?
Gosh, what did I just say?
Here. Can you stand up?
Wanna play?
It feels so warm.
Even in this cool breeze,
the inside of me feels nice and warm.
And when I take a deep breath
and exhale, I feel lighter somehow.
In both body and mind.
I've been thinking about it a lot...
and I guess I could go to the pool.
Episode 9 "Stepsister and Diary"
Saki...
Saki.
Saki?
Look. We're here.
They're so cute.
They're so cool!
Are you sure this is the one you want?
Yup! This is the one!
Growr!
Mommy, look at this!
Asamura, don't you work at a bookstore?
Do you really?
Wow!
Yeah.
Can you make a lot of money at a bookstore?
Well? Well?
Oh, I don't know.
Sounds great!
It's the first job I've ever had.
But all you've done over break is work
and study? That's so responsible!
Responsible! Mr. Responsible!
All I've done is sleep the whole time.
For real!
I'm not that responsible, though.
I'm the same way.
Aw, don't be modest!
Totally!
Today's the day.
I'm not really that good
at dealing with friends.
I'm always bad at reading the room.
But today actually wasn't too painful.
I think I have Asamura-kun to thank for that.
He's a lot better with people than I am.
But when he doesn't like
something, he just says so.
I think that's one of the reasons
I'm attracted to him.
Yahoo!
All right, now we're going to play
some kickboard Othello! It's super easy!
Okay!
Instead of trying to stand out,
he's always trying to make
sure everyone else has fun.
I thought that was really cool.
Even though it seems like
nobody else notices.
Maybe I'm the only one who does.
I don't know. That makes
me feel kind of proud...
What you just did...
That was really cool
and a little scared.
I mean, I don't want to become the center
of attention and then risk screwing up.
It's a team game, after all.
Really?
Well, ignoring the objective
reality of the situation,
subjectively, I wanted
to compliment you for it.
I just thought it was really cool.
Like a stagehand who's devoted
to assisting everyone.
Are stagehands really that cool, though?
Well, everyone's standards are different.
I guess that's true.
But if you keep talking like that,
I'm gonna get embarrassed.
No, that was it.
All right. Maybe I'll go swim a little more.
Let's go!
Okay!
Here!
Got it!
Uh-oh.
I like her.
Honestly, I've never been great with girls.
Probably because of how my mom and dad were.
It gave me a really cynical view of
relationships between men and women.
That's why I've never fallen in love
with anyone before now.
And yet...
This emotion, this feeling that most people
regard as so sacred and glorious...
How did it sneak up on me like this?
And why right now?
And why, of all people...
She's my little sister.
But she's also Ayase-san.
My...
little stepsister.
You and Maaya have sure gotten friendly.
Huh? Oh, yeah, I wanted to
thank her for the invitation.
She really took care of everything.
I had a great time.
Narasaka-san is pretty incredible.
Thank you.
Huh?
She's my friend. I'm happy to hear
that people appreciate her.
Did you have a good time?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've liked swimming at pools.
I hadn't been able to enjoy swimming
for a while, so this was really fun.
I'm really glad I listened to you, Asamura-kun.
I mean, I didn't really do anything.
Ayase-sa—
That sure startled me.
I did see a lot of people in yukata today.
Asamura-kun, I think you're incredibly
thoughtful and considerate.
Huh?
I really admire that.
You think so?
Yeah, I think so.
I realized this was my chance to say it.
You see how hard people try.
I know I said this at the pool,
but I think that part of you is really cool.
He shines so brightly in my life.
He looks so cool to me.
I think you're great...
Which is why...
Big Brother.
Um, sorry. Did I surprise you?
You're always taking care of me
and going out of your way for me.
You're someone I can truly rely on.
Like a real brother, you know?
I'm glad, Ayase-san.
But it still sounds kind of weird, huh?
I don't think so.
You don't?
Honestly, that was a close call.
Her calling me that, as unexpected as it was,
brought me back to my senses.
Ayase-san's friendly behavior, her praise...
It was all for her brother.
She trusts me.
Meanwhile, here I was,
trying to break all our rules.
I can't do this.
How am I supposed to act when I get home?
I hope he didn't notice how much
my hands were trembling.
I have to keep repeating it to myself.
The two of you are siblings, girl!
But maybe, just maybe...
If Asamura-kun did like me and
chose to share how he felt with me,
would I be able to fully reject those feelings?
I'm scared.
If he takes even one step forward,
I just know I would...
I would completely fall apart.
Friday, August 28th
Oh, Mom? What about work?
I took the day off.
Is Yuta still in bed?
He must be exhausted. Why don't
we let him sleep a little longer?
Saki-chan, do you have work again today?
I took yesterday and today off.
Did Yuta-kun, too?
Yeah.
Great! Then we can all spend
some time together!
The whole family!
I'm glad she's happy.
I want her to be happy enough
to make up for all the hard times.
So I... Yeah.
That's why I'm going to
lock away these feelings.
I don't want to spoil our parents' happiness.
I don't want to cause trouble for Asamura-kun.
I pray that nobody finds out how I feel.
Saki told us that you have
the day off from work.
That's right.
And at this point, you're a
confirmed cram school skipper, too!
You mean you knew about that
and still didn't wake me up?
This sort of thing is good
for you once in a while.
Thank you, Yuta-kun.
Huh?
For taking Saki to the pool.
Oh.
Actually, it was Ayase-san's
friend who invited us.
But if you hadn't dragged her along,
that girl probably wouldn't have gone.
You might be right about that.
I'm so glad you're her older brother.
Oh, that's right, Yuta-kun!
Saki's favorite thing!
Oh, what you mentioned before?
Yeah. I'll show you what it is.
Here.
Huh? This is it?
I'm back.
Welcome home! Ooh, that's new!
Welcome ho—
Whoa, you look totally different!
It looks great on you!
Yeah!
Welcome home, Ayase-san.
Thank you, Big Brother.
I pulled my diary out and
reread what I'd written so far.
I realized that I'd been much more blunt
and honest in my diary than I thought.
All of my thoughts about growing
more and more attracted to him
were spelled out right there on the page.
But my diary entries for this week
will only exist in my mind.
If I leave a written record,
there's always a chance that
he may find it someday.
I'm never going to write down
how I truly feel ever again.
When I want to relive my memories,
I'll do it inside my head.
I shouldn't spend my days trying to
connect with him as just some girl.
I'm only his little sister.
I have to live with him as his stepsister.
And in my life as his stepsister,
I don't need a diary anymore.
Episode 10 "Relations and Regrets"